A Guide to the Virginia Hummel Papers 1830-1998
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Box 3 1954-1997, n.d.
  - List of loans from 1874, photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 3-81)
  - Virginia Hummel's notes n.d. (Box-folder 3-82)
  - Article; "Blacksburg planning downtown pathway to tie into trail" n.d. (Box-folder 3-83)
  - Articles; "Dr. G. Burke Johnston's retirement and Memorial fund" n.d. (Box-folder 3-84)
  - Article; "Blacksburg bookstore closes" n.d. (Box-folder 3-85)
  - Article, "Highway bill brings I-73 via Roanoke" n.d. (Box-folder 3-86)
  - Article; "Beautifying Christiansburg" n.d. (Box-folder 3-87)
  - Article; "Drapers Meadow Massacre Happened 209 years ago" n.d. (Box-folder 3-88)
  - Articles; From Mountainside, Vol. 1, Nos. 3 and 4 n.d. (Box-folder 3-89)
  - Articles; Hot Springs and the Homestead n.d. (Box-folder 3-90)
  - Article; "Cook Favors buying Tract" n.d. (Box-folder 3-91)
  - Approval letter for the General Education Development n.d. (Box-folder 3-92)
  - Articles on churches in Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 3-93)
  - Articles; Raymond T. Hale will become the superintendent of schools in Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 3-94)
  - Article; "Mrs. Hill sets retirement after teaching 45 years," photocopiped n.d. (Box-folder 3-95)
  - Article; "Drama Students at 'U' taught by Yale coach" n.d. (Box-folder 3-96)
  - Articles about smokehouses n.d. (Box-folder 3-97)
  - Article; "W.E.D. Bodell, at the age of 99, still reads his daily newspaper" n.d. (Box-folder 3-98)
  - Article; "A Classic Thanksgiving celebration," Roanoke Times and World News n.d. (Box-folder 3-99)
  - Article; "Marvel on the mountain, William Preston's House" n.d. (Box-folder 3-100)
  - Articles; Philantropy 1983-84, meeting the needs of the people n.d. (Box-folder 3-101)
  - Article; "Customers of Blacksburg Store, 1825-28" n.d. (Box-folder 3-102)
  - Article; "The Antiquity of Blacksburg," Virginia Tech Engineer, Vol. 4, No. 1 n.d. (Box-folder 3-103)
  - William Addison Caldwell, honored with a room in Tech Student Center n.d. (Box-folder 3-104)
  - Story of Virginia: 1830-present, commonwealth studies project n.d. (Box-folder 3-105)
  - Study units in Little River, Christiansburg, Blacksburg, coal fields, Upper and Lower North Fork, South Fork n.d. (Box-folder 3-106)
  - Articles on buildings in Blacksburg being razed, oldest brick building and Evans house n.d. (Box-folder 3-107)
  - Raines Real Estate, Blacksburg, Va., Mountain View Estate n.d. (Box-folder 3-108)
  - Article; "History of New River Country explored - a review of the book The New River Early Settlement by Patricia Givens Johnson." n.d. (Box-folder 3-109)
  - The Virginia Census: A Guide n.d. (Box-folder 3-110)
  - Card Catalogue listings, Montgomery County, Va. n.d. (Box-folder 3-111)
  - Article; "News of activities during the past week by pupils at Blacksburg High School" n.d. (Box-folder 3-112)
  - Listing of books about the history of Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 3-113)
  - Blacksburg Business Directory n.d. (Box-folder 3-114)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, floor plan n.d. (Box-folder 3-115)
  - Article; "19th Century clerks office gets daily use," photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 3-116)
  - Article; "Blacksburg, Tech share 'Good life' by G. Burke Johnson," photocopied from Town and Campus n.d. (Box-folder 3-117)
  - Resolutions of respect for Mr. John M. Evans by the Masonic Lodge Hall n.d. (Box-folder 3-118)
  - German New River Settlement by Rev. U.S.A. Heavener M.A. n.d. (Box-folder 3-119)
  - Article; "A day in Court" n.d. (Box-folder 3-120)
  - Article; "Two Revolutionary Heroes" n.d. (Box-folder 3-121)
  - Article; "Tour Montgomery County's Historical Sites with the D.A.R." n.d. (Box-folder 3-122)
  - Article; "Blacksburg played role in Civil War" n.d. (Box-folder 3-123)
  - Article; "Blacksburg Marked by many firsts" n.d. (Box-folder 3-124)
  - Article; "Practical Holiday Gifts, advertisement by Thurman and Boone Company, Inc." n.d. (Box-folder 3-125)